Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - B
        - Belle Stars - Sign of the times, 1983; SR-11214; Belle Stars (Box 185)
          Catalog # 0-29657; A-side Matrix # B-17881-SH1
        - Belouis Some - Imagination, 1985; SR-11215; Belouis Some (Box 185)
          Catalog # V-8638; A-side Matrix # V1-8638-X6009-45A-21#2
        - Beloved - Your love takes me higher, 1988; SR-11216; Beloved (Box 185)
          Catalog # YZ357T; A-side Matrix # Y2-357T-A-1
          WEA Records
        - Beloved - Surprise me; Forever dancing, 1987; SR-11217; Beloved (Box 185)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # HARP-7(T)-AA2
          Flim Flam Productions
        - Beltram, Joey - The Beltram re-releases 1989-1991 (Disc one), 1994; SR-11218; Beltram, Joey (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11219. Double album
          Catalog # TX 5027; A-side Matrix # TX 5026A
        - Beltram, Joey - The Beltram re-releases 1989-1991 (Disc two), 1994; SR-11219; Beltram, Joey (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11218. Double album
          Catalog # TX 5027; A-side Matrix # TX 5026 C2
        - Ben, Jorge - O bidú: silêncio no brooklin, 1969; SR-11220; Ben, Jorge (Box 185)
          Catalog # COELP-40914; A-side Matrix # COELP-40914-A
          Copacabana
          Brazil
        - Ben, Jorge - África brasil, 1970; SR-11221; Ben, Jorge (Box 185)
          Catalog # 6349 187; A-side Matrix # 6349187 A1
          Philips
        - Ben, Jorge - A arte de Jorge Ben (Disc one), 1975; SR-11222; Ben, Jorge (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11223. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # 6470 535; A-side Matrix # 6470 536 A1
          Fontana
        - Ben, Jorge - A arte de Jorge Ben (Disc two), 1975; SR-11223; Ben, Jorge (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11222. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # 6470 535; A-side Matrix # 6470 535 A1
        - Benatar, Pat - Sex as a weapon, 1985; SR-11224; Benatar, Pat (Box 185)
          Catalog # 4V9 42917; A-side Matrix # 4V9-42917-AS-P1
        - Benatar, Pat - Love is a battlefield, 1983; SR-11225; Benatar, Pat (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11226. 2 copies
          Catalog # 4V9 42734; A-side Matrix # 4V9-42734-AS-CP1
        - Benatar, Pat - Love is a battlefield, 1983; SR-11226; Benatar, Pat (Box 185)
          In same jacket as # SR-11225. 2 copies
        - Bender, Steve - The final thing, 1977; SR-11227; Bender, Steve (Box 185)
          Catalog # Disco 3003; A-side Matrix # ZXDR-60629-12X
          London Disco
        - Beneficence - Sucka's brevity, 1994; SR-11228; Beneficence (Box 186)
          Catalog # BHR 504; A-side Matrix # BHR 504-A
          Big House Records
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Benerim - Dogz on da set; Step, SR-11229; Benerim (Box 186)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # J4K 11 A2
          24 Karat Records
        - Benét, Eric - Georgy porgy, 1999; SR-11230; Benét, Eric (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11231. 2 copies
          Catalog # PRO-A-9625; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9625-A SR1
        - Benét, Eric - Georgy porgy, 1999; SR-11231; Benét, Eric (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11230. 2 copies
        - Benét, Eric - Spiritual thang, 1996; SR-11232; Benét, Eric (Box 186)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8468; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8468-A-SR-1
        - Benét, Eric - Spiritual thang, 1996; SR-11233; Benét, Eric (Box 186)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8506; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8506/0-43793 A SK3
        - Benson, George - Weekend in L.A. (Disc two), 1978; SR-12793; Benson, George (Box 186)
          Catalog # 2WB 3139; A-side Matrix # 2-WB-2-3139 Record 2 WW-1 112
        - Franklin, Aretha - Sparkle, 1976; SR-12794; Franklin, Aretha; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 186)
          Catalog # SD 18176; A-side Matrix # ST-A-763613C
        - Benson, George - In flight, 1977; SR-11234; Benson, George (Box 186)
          Catalog # BSK 2983; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-2983 WW3
        - Benson, George - Love x love, 1980; SR-11235; Benson, George (Box 186)
          Catalog # PRO-A-905; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-905-A1
        - Benson, George - The George Benson collection (Disc one), 1981; SR-11236; Benson, George (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11237. Double album
          Catalog # 2HW 3577; A-side Matrix # 2HW-1-3577 SR1
        - Benson, George - The George Benson collection (Disc two), 1981; SR-11237; Benson, George (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11236. Double album
          Catalog # 2HW 3577; A-side Matrix # 2HW-1-3577 SR3
        - Benson, George - Space, 1978; SR-11238; Benson, George (Box 186)
          Catalog # CTI 7085; A-side Matrix # RVG-87750-A-3
        - Bentley Rhythm Ace - Midlander (there can only be one), 1997; SR-11239; Bentley Rhythm Ace (Box 186)
          Catalog # SKINT 23; A-side Matrix # SKINT 23A1
          Skint
        - Benzino - Rock the party, 2002; SR-11240; Benzino (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11241. 2 copies
          Catalog # 67330-0; A-side Matrix # ST-E-67330-A-1
        - Benzino - Rock the party, 2002; SR-11241; Benzino (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11240. 2 copies
        - Camafeu De Oxóssi - Berimbau, 1989; SR-11242; Camafeu De Oxóssi (Box 186)
          Catalog # 0.24.405.019; A-side Matrix # 024405019A
          Phonodisc
        - Berlin - No more words; Dancing in Berlin, 1984; SR-11243; Berlin (Box 186)
          Catalog # 0-20195; A-side Matrix # 0-20195-A SH-2
        - Berlin, Max - Max Berlin's world wide party, 1979; SR-11244; Berlin, Max (Box 186)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # EMLP 7502A
          Emergency Records
        - Berné, Jacqui - It's been so long, 1987; SR-11245; Berné, Jacqui (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11246. 2 copies
          Catalog # HYT 2; A-side Matrix # HYTT-2-A2
          Hi Hat
        - Berné, Jacqui - It's been so long, 1987; SR-11246; Berné, Jacqui (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11245. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Beroard, Jocelyne - Siwo, 1986; SR-11247; Beroard, Jocelyne (Box 186)
          Catalog # GD 36; A-side Matrix # GD 036 A
          GD Productions
          Paris, France
        - Beroard, Jocelyne - Milans, 1991; SR-11248; Beroard, Jocelyne (Box 186)
          Catalog # 468723 1; A-side Matrix # 14 4687323-20 1A 1
        - Beroshima & Ishino - Matadors of techno EP, 1999; SR-11249; Beroshima & Ishino (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11250. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # LC 0725; A-side Matrix # MULLER 2018
          Müller Records
        - Beroshima & Ishino - Matadors of techno EP, 1999; SR-11250; Beroshima & Ishino (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11249. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Beroshima & Ishino - Technovain, 1997; SR-11251; Beroshima & Ishino (Box 186)
          Catalog # 29701-6; A-side Matrix # MULLER 2001 A2
        - Beroshima - The pornographic of performance, 1997; SR-11252; Beroshima (Box 186)
          Catalog # MULLER RECORDS 2007; A-side Matrix # MULLER 2007
        - Beroshima - Technovain, 1996; SR-11253; Beroshima (Box 186)
          Catalog # LC 4660; A-side Matrix # MULLER 2001 A2
        - Beroshima - The lost freakquencies volume 2 EP, 1998; SR-11254; Beroshima (Box 186)
          Catalog # MUELLER 2014; A-side Matrix # MULLER 2014
        - Beroshima - Deebeephunky, 1997; SR-11255; Beroshima (Box 186)
          Catalog # MUELLER 2003; A-side Matrix # MULLER 2003
        - Berryman, Andre - The world according to Dré, 1988; SR-11256; Berryman, Andre (Box 186)
          Catalog # Z 44028; A-side Matrix # PAL-44028-1B G1
          Tabu Records
        - Bertei, Adele - Build me a bridge, 1983; SR-11257; Bertei, Adele (Box 186)
          Catalog # 0-20128; A-side Matrix # 0-20128-A-SH1
        - Beside - Odeon, 1984; SR-11258; Beside; Bambaataa, Afrika (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11259. 2 copies
          Catalog # 8342; A-side Matrix # 8342 A
          Carrere
        - Beside - Odeon, 1984; SR-11259; Beside; Bambaataa, Afrika (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11258. 2 copies
        - Betty Boo - Doin' the do, 1990; SR-11260; Betty Boo (Box 186)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4450; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 4450 RE1 3R1
          Sire
        - Between Two - Feel like makin' love, 1988; SR-11261; Between Two (Box 186)
          Catalog # 49 07580; A-side Matrix # XSS-177732-1A
        - Bevan, Craig - One better, 1983; SR-11262; Bevan, Craig (Box 186)
          Catalog # BS 002; A-side Matrix # BS-002 A
          Black Suit Records
        - B.E.W.A.R.E. - Pick up the pieces, 1988; SR-11263; B.E.W.A.R.E.; Scott, Toni (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11264. 2 copies
          Catalog # RHYTHM 003; A-side Matrix # RR 003-A
          Rhythm Records
          Amsterdam, Netherlands
        - B.E.W.A.R.E. - Pick up the pieces, 1988; SR-11264; B.E.W.A.R.E.; Scott, Toni (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11263. 2 copies
        - Beyoncé - Krazy in luv, 2003; SR-11265; Beyoncé (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11266. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # 44 79947; A-side Matrix # XSS-79947A-1A
        - Beyoncé - Krazy in luv, 2003; SR-11266; Beyoncé (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11265. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Beyond Reality - Whatever; Overstandings, 1997; SR-11267; Beyond Reality; Source of Labor (Box 186)
          Catalog # jmgv1; A-side Matrix # S35314 RE2
          Jasiri Media Group
        - BFX - Wonder, 2000; SR-11268; BFX (Box 186)
          Catalog # MFC 002; A-side Matrix # MFC-002A
          Made From Concrete
        - B.G. - Chopper in the city ghetto, 1999; SR-11269; B.G. (Box 186)
          Catalog # U8P 1559; A-side Matrix # U8P-1559-A
        - B.G. - I know, 2000; SR-11270; B.G. (Box 186)
          Catalog # UNIR-20321-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20321-1-A
        - B.G. - Move around, 2006; SR-11271; B.G.; Mannie Fresh (Box 186)
          Catalog # KOC-12-5849; A-side Matrix # KOC-12-5849-A
          Kock Entertainment
        - B.G. - X & Henne, 2000; SR-11272; B.G. (Box 186)
          Catalog # UNIR 20333-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR 20333-1A
        - B.G. - Cash money is an army, 1998; SR-11273; B.G. (Box 186)
          Catalog # U8P 1354; A-side Matrix # U8P-1354-A
        - B.G. - Bling bling, 1999; SR-11274; B.G. (Box 186)
          Catalog # U8P 1555; A-side Matrix # U8P-1555-A-RE1
        - B.G. Knocc Out - 50/50 luv, 1995; SR-11275; B.G. Knocc Out; Dresta (Box 186)
          Catalog # BHA-1; A-side Matrix # BGA-1 A DEF JAM
          Outburst Records
        - Bianca - My emotions, 1989; SR-11276; Bianca (Box 186)
          Catalog # 0-21317; A-side Matrix # 0-21317-A-SR1
        - Bianco, Matt - Don't blame it on that girl, 1988; SR-11277; Bianco, Matt (Box 186)
          Catalog # DMD 1243; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-55973-55559-1
        - Biddell, Kerrie - Kerrie Biddell, 1973; SR-11278; Biddell, Kerrie (Box 186)
          Catalog # BLA 030; A-side Matrix # BLA-030-1
          Bootleg
          Australia
        - Biddu Orchestra - Blue-eyed Soul, 1975; SR-11279; Biddu Orchestra (Box 186)
          Catalog # ES 90313; A-side Matrix # 90313A-1A-2-E
        - Bif Naked - Lucky (Disc One), 2000; SR-11280; Bif Naked (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11601. Double album
          Catalog # DMD 2558; A-side Matrix # DMD-89674-89675-1
        - Bif Naked - Lucky (Disc Two), 2000; SR-11601; Bif Naked (Box 186)
          In same jacket as # SR-11280. Double album
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Other 99, 1988; SR-11602; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # 44 08133; A-side Matrix # XSS-08133-A-DMM1A
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Tighten up volume '88, 1988; SR-11603; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # C 44074; A-side Matrix # AL-44074-1A
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Hollywood boulevard, 1986; SR-11604; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # CAS 02697; A-side Matrix # XSS-175951-1A
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Just play music!, 1988; SR-11605; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # 44 07851; A-side Matrix # XSS-07851A-1A G1
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Medicine show (US remix), 1985; SR-11606; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # 44-05359; A-side Matrix # XSS 174996-1A
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Bad, 1985; SR-11607; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11608. 2 copies
          Catalog # 44-05324; A-side Matrix # XSS-174831-1A
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Bad, 1985; SR-11608; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11607. 2 copies
          Catalog # 44-05324; A-side Matrix # XSS-174831-1B
        - Big Audio Dynamite - Hollywood boulevard, 1986; SR-11609; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # 44-06780; A-side Matrix # XSS-175950-1A
        - Big Audio Dynamite - C'mon every beatbox, 1986; SR-11610; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # 44-05963; A-side Matrix # XSS-175461-1A
        - Big Audio Dynamite - E = MC²; A party, 1985; SR-11611; Big Audio Dynamite (Box 187)
          Catalog # 44-05909; A-side Matrix # XSS-175173-1A
        - Big Blac - Pimp walk, 2000; SR-11612; Big Blac (Box 187)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # PIMPWALK A
          Tony Mercedes Records
          Fayetteville, Georgia
        - Big Boys - Fun, fun, fun…, 1982; SR-11613; Big Boys (Box 187)
          Catalog # BB-001; A-side Matrix # BB-001-A
          Moment Productions
        - Big Bub - Need your love remix, 1997; SR-11614; Big Bub (Box 187)
          Catalog # U8P-1235; A-side Matrix # U8P-1235A
        - Big D - Drop your guns; Payin the cost, 1995; SR-11615; Big D (Box 187)
          Catalog # TR 149; A-side Matrix # TR 149-A
          Trumpet Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Big Daddy Kane - I'll take you there; Wrath of kane, 1998; SR-11616; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11617. 2 copies
          Catalog # 0-21082; A-side Matrix # 0-21082-A-SH1
        - Big Daddy Kane - I'll take you there; Wrath of kane, 1998; SR-11617; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11616. 2 copies
        - Big D - Drop your guns; Payin the cost, 1995; SR-11618; Big D (Box 187)
        - Big D - Drop your guns; Payin the cost, 1995; SR-11619; Big D (Box 187)
        - Big Daddy Kane - In the PJ's; Show and prove, 1994; SR-11620; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11621. 2 copies
          Catalog # MCA8P 3070; A-side Matrix # MCA 12011 FDS-2
        - Big Daddy Kane - In the PJ's; Show and prove, 1994; SR-11621; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11620. 2 copies
        - Big Daddy Kane - Uncut, pure; Earth, wind, & fire, 1998; SR-11622; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11623. 2 copies
          Catalog # TL-002; A-side Matrix # TD-002-A
          The Label Records
        - Big Daddy Kane - Uncut, pure; Earth, wind, & fire, 1998; SR-11623; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11622. 2 copies
        - Big Daddy Kane - In the PJ's; Show and prove, 1994; SR-11624; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
        - Big Daddy Kane - Stop shammin'; Brother man brother man, 1993; SR-11625; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          Catalog # PRO-A-6350; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 6350 SR1
          Cold Chillin'
        - Big Daddy Kane - Uncut, pure; Da good tymz, 1998; SR-11626; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          Catalog # BRLP-1000; A-side Matrix # BRLT-1000-A
        - Big Daddy Kane - In the PJ's, 1994; SR-11627; Big Daddy Kane (Box 187)
          Catalog # MCA12 54885; A-side Matrix # MCA12015 FDS-1
        - Big Doc - Da tilt, 1995; SR-11628; Big Doc (Box 187)
          Catalog # SPRO 50857; A-side Matrix # PVL-53186-ARE1
          Scarface Records
        - Big Doc - Da tilt, 1995; SR-11629; Big Doc (Box 187)
        - Big Doc - Da tilt, 1995; SR-11630; Big Doc (Box 187)
        - Big Fella - These MC's, 2000; SR-11631; Big Fella (Box 187)
          Catalog # CDR-121-1P; A-side Matrix # 25 CDR-121-1 A
          Chrome Dope Records
          Brentwood, New York
        - Big Foot - I apologize (for taking you for granted), SR-11632; Big Foot (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11633. 2 copies
          Catalog # SRI-1124; A-side Matrix # SRI-1124-A
          Sue International Inc
        - Big Foot - I apologize (for taking you for granted), SR-11633; Big Foot (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11632. 2 copies
        - Big Foot - Foots world; Legacy of rage, 1999; SR-11634; Big Foot (Box 187)
          Catalog # BDS-809; A-side Matrix # BDS-809-A
          Cybertek Records
        - Big Fun - Stomp, 1993; SR-11635; Big Fun (Box 187)
          Catalog # IM-25035-1; A-side Matrix # 72787-25035-1 A
          ä
        - Big Johnson - To tha' beat, 1998; SR-11636; Big Johnson (Box 187)
          Catalog # MM 88452-1; A-side Matrix # MM 88452 A
          Moonshine Music
        - Big Kap - Da ladies in the house, 1995; SR-11637; Big Kap; Da Ladies (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11638. 2 copies
          Catalog # TB 691; A-side Matrix # TB-691-A
        - Big Kap - Da ladies in the house, 1995; SR-11638; Big Kap; Da Ladies (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11637. 2 copies
        - Big Kev - Menage et toi, 2001; SR-11639; Big Kev (Box 187)
          Catalog # PAY 2001; A-side Matrix # PAY2001-A
          Pay Up Records
        - Big L - Put it on, 1994; SR-11640; Big L (Box 187)
          Catalog # ACD 77728; A-side Matrix # XSS-77728-A
        - Big L - Put it on, 1994; SR-11641; Big L (Box 187)
        - Big Mello - Wind me up, 1994; SR-11642; Big Mello (Box 187)
          Catalog # SPRO 50790; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50790
          Rap-A-Lot Records
          Houston, Texas
        - Big Mello - Hot club wax, 1994; SR-11643; Big Mello; Hot Club Wax (Box 187)
          Catalog # SPRO 50775; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50775 A RE1
        - Big Mike - Hustlers; Sunday morning, 1999; SR-11644; Big Mike (Box 187)
          Catalog # 7087 6 13679 1 1; A-side Matrix # SPRO-70876-12679-1-1-A
        - Big Noyd - Usual suspect, 1996; SR-11645; Big Noyd (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11646. 2 copies
          Catalog # TB 755; A-side Matrix # TB-755-A
        - Big Noyd - Usual suspect, 1996; SR-11646; Big Noyd (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11645. 2 copies
        - Big Pig - Hungry town, 1987; SR-11647; Big Pig (Box 187)
          Catalog # AMY 409; A-side Matrix # AMY 409 A
        - Big Pig - Hungry town, 1988; SR-11648; Big Pig (Box 187)
          Catalog # SP-12270; A-side Matrix # A&M SP-012270-A-ES2
        - Big Pokey - Ball-n' parlay; Hardest pit, 1999; SR-11649; Big Pokey (Box 187)
          Catalog # U8P 1626; A-side Matrix # U8P-1626-A
        - Big Punisher - Capital punishment (Disc one), 1998; SR-11650; Big Punisher; Fat Joe (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11651. Double album
          Catalog # 07863-67512-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-67512-1-A
        - Big Punisher - Capital punishment (Disc two), 1998; SR-11651; Big Punisher; Fat Joe (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11650. Double album
          Catalog # 07863-67512-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-67512-1-C
        - Big Punisher - Capital punishment (Disc two), 1998; SR-11652; Big Punisher; Fat Joe (Box 187)
          Catalog # RDAB-67648-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-67648-1C
        - Big Punisher - Capital punishment (Disc one), 1998; SR-11653; Big Punisher; Fat Joe (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11654; SR-11655. Double album; 2 copies
          Catalog # RDAB-67648-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-67648-1A
        - Big Punisher - Capital punishment (Disc one), 1998; SR-11654; Big Punisher; Fat Joe (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11653; SR-11655. Double album; 2 copies
        - Big Punisher - Capital punishment (Disc two), 1998; SR-11655; Big Punisher; Fat Joe (Box 187)
          In same jacket as # SR-11653; SR-11654. Double album
        - Big Punisher - Mamma; Brave in the heart, 2001; SR-11656; Big Punisher (Box 188)
          Catalog # RPROLP-4511; A-side Matrix # 88561-9059-1 A
        - Big Punisher - Yeeeah baby, 2000; SR-11657; Big Punisher (Box 188)
          In same jacket as # SR-11658. Double album
          Catalog # C 63869; A-side Matrix # AL-63869-1B
        - Big Punisher - Yeeeah baby, 2000; SR-11658; Big Punisher (Box 188)
          In same jacket as # SR-11657. Double album
        - Big Punisher - Makes me sweat, 1998; SR-11659; Big Punisher; Beenie Man (Box 188)
          Catalog # MCA8P 4267; A-side Matrix # MCA-13302
          Flyte Tyme Records
        - Big Punisher - Punish me, 1998; SR-11660; Big Punisher (Box 188)
          Catalog # RDAB-65640-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-65640-1A-RE
        - Big Punisher - It's so hard, 2000; SR-11661; Big Punisher (Box 188)
          Catalog # RPROLP 4394; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-4394A
        - Big Rob - Treason, 1996; SR-11662; Big Rob; Little Sprout (Box 188)
          Catalog # YBR578; A-side Matrix # YBR 578A
          Uprising Records
          Long Island, New York
        - Big Scoob - Suckaz can't hang, 1994; SR-11663; Big Scoob (Box 188)
          Catalog # PROCC2025; A-side Matrix # CC-2025-A
        - Big Shug - Treat u better, 1995; SR-11664; Big Shug (Box 188)
          Catalog # Y-58231; A-side Matrix # Y-58231-A
        - Big Shug - Crush, 1996; SR-11665; Big Shug (Box 188)
          Catalog # 697-120-088-1; A-side Matrix # 697-120-0881A
          Payday
        - Big Squig - Keep it going, 1995; SR-11666; Big Squig (Box 188)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # NR-004AD A
          Darkside Entertainment
          Cleveland, Ohio
        - Big T - Unknown, SR-11667; Big T (Box 188)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # B403756-01 A1 MK
          Low Spirit Recordings
          Berlin, Germany
        - Big Tabb - Raw dawg, 1996; SR-11668; Big Tabb (Box 188)
          Catalog # RR96; A-side Matrix # RR-96-A
          Ragz to Riches Entertainment
        - Big Tony and the T.F. Crew - Back doing what we do best "live", SR-11669; Big Tony and the T.F. Crew (Box 188)
          Catalog # TDE 3023; A-side Matrix # TED-3023-A
          T.T.E.D. Records
        - Big Tony and the T.F. Crew - Let's party, 1987; SR-11670; Big Tony and the T.F. Crew (Box 188)
          Catalog # TDE -3027; A-side Matrix # TDE-3027-A
        - Big Tony and the T.F. Crew - Go-go lady, 1988; SR-11671; Big Tony and the T.F. Crew (Box 188)
          Catalog # TDE-3030; A-side Matrix # TDE-3030-A 1-1
          Go-Go USA Records
        - Big Tymers - Big ballin', 1998; SR-11672; Big Tymers (Box 188)
          Catalog # U8P 1405; A-side Matrix # U8P-1405 A
        - Big Tymers - #1 Stunna, 2000; SR-11673; Big Tymers (Box 188)
          Catalog # UNIR-20234-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20234-1-A
        - Big Tymers - 10 wayz, 2000; SR-11674; Big Tymers (Box 188)
          Catalog # UNIR-20329-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20329-1-A
        - Big Tymers - Stun'n, 1998; SR-11675; Big Tymers (Box 188)
          Catalog # U8P 1327; A-side Matrix # U8P-1327 A RE1
        - Big Tymers - Get your roll on, 2000; SR-11676; Big Tymers (Box 188)
          Catalog # UNIR-20072-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20072-1-A
        - Big Tymers - How you luv that? Volume 2, 1999; SR-11677; Big Tymers (Box 188)
          Catalog # U8P 1466; A-side Matrix # U8P-1466-A
        - Big Yang - Now it's time, 1994; SR-11678; Big Yang (Box 188)
          Catalog # MOBB0102; A-side Matrix # MOBB-0102-A
          M.O.B.B. Records
        - Big Yang - Now it's time, 1994; SR-11679; Big Yang (Box 188)
        - Bigalows - Dance, dance, dance, (werr gunna), 1983; SR-11680; Bigalows (Box 188)
          Catalog # AS 1704; A-side Matrix # XSM-171274 AB
          Bobcat Records